[{"answer": "I think you're a damn fool", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "my friend is eight and I'm not married to her mother.  I can't even remember her mother's name.", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Don't let her.  I believe in this, I completely believe in this.  It happened to that place, at least six times", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Yes!  Who was she", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "No one ever even looks at me.  They don't.  On top of which, who are they? They could like the symphony.  I could never fall in love with someone who likes to go to the symphony", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "The illustrations are han", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "It's why it's  so much", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "So Foxbooks can..", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " Here you go", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I can't believe it.  I saw my friend", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Maybe he's in that place, but today he was in that place.  The most brilliant and reclusive novelist in the history of the world is here, in this neighborhood.  He may be living on this very block", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I mean, we're fine", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "We're fine", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Hi", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Of course I remember you", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "-- were with. ", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "The entrance to our store is around the corner.  There is no other way to say it. It's not the name of our store, it's where it is.  You don't own", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Twinkle lights", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "How do you know that", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "in the book business", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No, I don't need any money.  Thank you very much", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Nothing", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Yes.  Yes I am.  That's exactly what I'm going to do.  Why not", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "The first day you lied to me", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You did too", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I didn't lie to you", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I did not", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "They hit something and you slam right into that plastic partition", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Or he could be in the hospital in one of those sem", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "-- but he got only one call and he had to use it to call his lawyer", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "You could be dead", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Are you crazy?  This man couldn't possibly be the rooftop killer", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "That was different", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Why not", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "In the last mayoral election, when my friend was running against my friend, I went to get a manicure and forgot to vote", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Oh, I suppose you could never be with a woman who gets manicures", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "It's not that, my friend, really it's not. It's just... my friend..", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "What was", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": " -- and in a week, it will be something really depressing, like a Baby Gap.  I am being amazingly brave", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I don't know.  I'm going to take some time.  I have a little money saved.  I'm almost looking forward to it", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Maybe you can make up on my friend.  That would be so great for the book", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "If I ever get out of here, I'm having my eyes lasered", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "I heard you were sick and I was worried and I wanted to", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Because I have plans, I have lots of offers.  I've been offered a job by", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Former", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "I will", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Goodbye", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "His IQ", "docId": "Youve_got_mail.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "The number of times he's seen The Godfather", "qsentId": 54}]